{
    "subject": "resource/Lightning_Strikes_Twice_(1934_film)",
    "predicate": "property/hasPhotoCollection",
    "object": "http://wifo5-03.informatik.uni-mannheim.de/flickrwrappr/photos/Lightning_Strikes_Twice_(1934_film)",
    "human_readable": "The film Lightning Strikes Twice (1934) has a photo collection.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9766186475753784,
            "question": "Does the film Lightning Strikes Twice have a photo collection?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9076341390609741,
            "question": "What kind of collection does the film Lightning Strikes Twice have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8969881534576416,
            "question": "Can you find any information about the photos in the collection for Lightning Strikes Twice?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8131972551345825,
            "question": "What kind of movie is Lightning Strikes Twice?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7948955297470093,
            "question": "Are there any famous people featured in the photo collection from Lightning Strikes Twice?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7515227198600769,
            "question": "What is the plot of the movie Lightning Strikes Twice?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7349041700363159,
            "question": "What year was the film Lightning Strikes Twice released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5887316465377808,
            "question": "Who are some actors who might have been in the film Lightning Strikes Twice?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5844597816467285,
            "question": "Are there any awards or recognitions associated with the film Lightning Strikes Twice?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44467833638191223,
            "question": "Is there any information about the director or production team of Lightning Strikes Twice?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The film Lightning Strikes Twice (1934) has a photo collection.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4165_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any awards or recognitions associated with the film Lightning Strikes Twice?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4165_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some actors who might have been in the film Lightning Strikes Twice?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4165_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was the film Lightning Strikes Twice released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4165_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4165_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4165_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4165_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4165_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4165_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4165_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4165_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4165_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4165_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4165_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the format you requested:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because the document with file_path \"/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4165/re-ranker-msmarco/29.txt\" contains information about a photo collection related to the film Lightning Strikes Twice (1934), including dimensions, date taken, and photographer."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the film \"Lightning Strikes Twice\" from 1934, including details about its release date and plot. Additionally, there is mention of a photograph related to the movie, supporting the statement that the film has a photo collection."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information suggesting a photo collection for the film Lightning Strikes Twice (1934) in the given context.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}